{
    "subject": "resource/The_Simpsons",
    "predicate": "ontology/company",
    "object": "resource/Klasky_Csupo",
    "human_readable": "The Simpsons was founded by Klasky Csupo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8492588996887207,
            "question": "Who founded The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.595572292804718,
            "question": "What company created The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3267878293991089,
            "question": "Is Klasky Csupo known for creating other animated shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30077803134918213,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2897699773311615,
            "question": "When was The Simpsons first aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2169373482465744,
            "question": "Where is The Simpsons set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21642576158046722,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20723742246627808,
            "question": "What genre is The Simpsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13162532448768616,
            "question": "Has The Simpsons won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11093288660049438,
            "question": "Is The Simpsons still running today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Simpsons was founded by Klasky Csupo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6300_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has The Simpsons won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6300_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Simpsons?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6300_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in The Simpsons?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6300_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6300_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear evidence that the company Klasky Csupo created \"The Simpsons,\" which strongly supports the statement that \"The Simpsons\" was founded by Klasky Csupo. The information is directly mentioned in multiple documents, confirming this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}